{
    "quizzes": [
        {
            "title": "week7",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "index": 1,
                    "question": "The price of a good that prevails in the world market for that good is the definition of",
                    "options": ["export price", "import price", "world price", "domestic price"],
                    "correct": "world price"
                },
                {
                    "index": 2,
                    "question": "The area between the demand curve and the price is an indicator of",
                    "options": ["consumer surplus", "producer surplus", "total surplus", "deadweight loss"],
                    "correct": "consumer surplus"
                },
                {
                    "index": 3,
                    "question": "The amount a buyer is willing to pay for a good minus the amount the buyer actually pays for it is",
                    "options": ["consumer surplus", "producer surplus", "total surplus", "deadweight loss"],
                    "correct": "consumer surplus"
                },
                {
                    "index": 4,
                    "question": "The amount a seller is paid for a good minus the seller’s cost of providing it is",
                    "options": ["consumer surplus", "producer surplus", "total surplus", "deadweight loss"],
                    "correct": "producer surplus"
                },
                {
                    "index": 5,
                    "question": "Value to buyers - Cost to sellers is",
                    "options": ["consumer surplus", "producer surplus", "total surplus", "deadweight loss"],
                    "correct": "total surplus"
                },
                {
                    "index": 6,
                    "question": "The fall in total surplus that results from a market distortion, such as a tax is",
                    "options": ["consumer surplus", "producer surplus", "total surplus", "deadweight loss"],
                    "correct": "deadweight loss"
                },
                {
                    "index": 7,
                    "question": "Laffer's curve is the relationship between",
                    "options": ["inflation and unemployment", "tax size and tax revenue", "producer surplus and consumer surplus", "tax size and deadweight loss"],
                    "correct": "tax size and tax revenue"
                },
                {
                    "index": 8,
                    "question": "Imposition of tariff",
                    "options": [
                        "increases producer surplus and government revenue",
                        "increases consumer surplus and government revenue",
                        "increases producer surplus, consumer surplus and government revenue",
                        "increases total surplus"
                    ],
                    "correct": "increases producer surplus and government revenue"
                },
                {
                    "index": 9,
                    "question": "The maximum amount that a buyer will pay for a good is",
                    "options": ["willingness to pay", "market demand", "demand curve", "buyer’s surplus"],
                    "correct": "willingness to pay"
                },
                {
                    "index": 10,
                    "question": "The area between the supply curve and the price is an indicator of",
                    "options": ["consumer surplus", "producer surplus", "total surplus", "deadweight loss"],
                    "correct": "producer surplus"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
